{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.3","schemaVersion":"","author":"Rachel N. Lagrange","title":"Introduction to the Adobe Photoshop Workspace","description":"E-learning course introducing learners to the Adobe Photoshop workspace, elements, and more. This course is based on Adobe Photoshop CC 2025, and created using Adobe Captivate Classic.","email":"rlagra2@wgu.edu","website":"https://hrogue143.github.io/PS1001/","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":46274,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":74,"width":896,"height":504,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Image_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_45","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_1","title":"Introduction to the Adobe Photoshop Workspace    Course Length: 45 minutes  In this course, you’ll get hands-on with the core interface components you need to start navigating Photoshop.  (c) 2025    MADE IN ADOBE CAPTIVATE CLASSIC                          Author:  Rachel N. Lagrange, Certified Adobe Educator (Lvl 2)  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si26877","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si26906","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide7703","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Course Introduction","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":483},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7703"}}},{"id":"Image_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_71","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_7","title":"Please fill out the following information: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_124","title":"What is your Name? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_3","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_6","title":"Save ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si204294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Save ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si204307","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Save ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_129","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_129","title":"What is your email? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_4","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Button_7","title":"Save ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si204336","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Save ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si204349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Save ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide203976","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Student Information","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":588},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide203976"}}},{"id":"Image_123","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_123","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_4","title":"By the end of this course, you will be able to: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"Identify and label main workspace components in Adobe Photoshop ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_6","title":"Navigate the Essentials default workspace inside of Adobe Photoshop ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_7","title":"Reset, customize and save a workspace inside of Adobe Photoshop ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"Pass a Quiz of 15 questions with a score of 80% or higher ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7757","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Course Objectives","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":522},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7757"}}},{"id":"Image_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_47","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"This is the Photoshop Home Screen. Anytime you open Photoshop, it will look like this.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_69","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"This is the Photoshop Home Screen. Anytime you open Photoshop, it will look like this. Go ahead and click on the Ps logo in the top lefthand corner of the Home Screen. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_1","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide7932","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Photoshop Home Screen","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":588},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7932"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"Clicking the Ps logo on the Home Screen brings you into the main Workspace. Right now there is no project open so it doesn’t seem like much yet. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_76","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_76","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_82","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":"The first time Photoshop is opened, it automatically shows the Essentials Workspace.  When a project is open, you can really start to see some of the tools and options available. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8494","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Photoshop Workspace","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":717},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8494"}}},{"id":"Image_80","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_80","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_9","title":"The Essentials Workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_62","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si279666","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si279695","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide233903","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"The Essentials Workspace","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":225},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide233903"}}},{"id":"Image_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_83","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_165","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_165","title":"The Essentials workspace in Photoshop is the default, general-purpose layout designed for many tasks. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_166","title":"The Essentials Workspace features common tools and panels that offer an uncluttered, efficient starting point for beginners and pros alike, with customizable panels to fit specific workflows. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_167","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_167","title":"It's the standard view you see when you first open Photoshop, balancing core functions for day-to-day editing.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide246390","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace with no project","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":891},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide246390"}}},{"id":"Image_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_35","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_60","title":"Let’s start with the Home Button. It looks like a house and is located in the top left corner of your workspace. Go ahead and click the Home Button to learn more. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_29","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si104197","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si104226","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_100","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_100","title":"The Home Button takes you back to Photoshop’s Home Screen, where you can open recent files, browse presets, and access Learn tutorials. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17712","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Home Button","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":639},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17712"}}},{"id":"Image_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_54","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_61","title":"The Menu Bar is the top-most horizontal bar in your Workspace. Click on the Menu Bar to learn more about it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_3","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_28","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si104065","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si104094","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_101","title":"The Menu Bar contains multiple drop-down menus (“File,” “Edit,” etc.). These menus give you access to every command and feature in Photoshop. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18364","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Menu Bar","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":573},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18364"}}},{"id":"Image_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_55","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_62","title":"Next, let’s look at the Toolbar on the left-hand side of our screen.  Click on the Toolbar to learn more about it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si29268","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si29297","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_102","title":"The Toolbar is the vertical strip of tool icons (on the left by default) for all your drawing, selection, and editing tools. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18481","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Toolbar","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":585},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18481"}}},{"id":"Image_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_56","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"The horizontal bar right under the Menu Bar is called the Options Bar. Click on the Options Bar to learn more about it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si29683","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si29712","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_103","title":"The Options Bar will display settings specific to whichever tool is active (for example, brush size and hardness when the Brush tool is selected). ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18590","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Options Bar","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":729},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18590"}}},{"id":"Image_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_57","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":"Now look on the right-hand side of the screen. This is called your Panel Dock. There are Collapsed and Expanded Panels located here. Click on the Collapsed Panels to learn more. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_6","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_111","title":"Collapsed Panels are the minimized panel icons that hide their contents until you need them.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si29815","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si29844","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide18709","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":648},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18709"}}},{"id":"Image_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_58","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_113","title":"The other side of the Panel Dock has Expanded Panels already open for you to access. Click on the Expanded Panels to learn more. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_17","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_34","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si195211","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si195226","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_115","title":"Expanded Panels are a fully open panel group showing all controls - like Layers, Properties, and Adjustments - so you can access detailed settings. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide195340","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":660},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide195340"}}},{"id":"Image_119","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_119","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"Like what you would call it in traditional art, this is the Canvas on which your project is created. Click anywhere within the Canvas to learn more. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30242","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30271","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_105","title":"The Canvas is the central area that opens and shows where your project image’s pixels actually live—this is where you paint, edit, and compose. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide18836","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Canvas","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":660},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide18836"}}},{"id":"Image_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_60","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":"The Document Window contains all the visual workspace for that file. Click anywhere in the Document Window to learn more about it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_20","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si29978","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30007","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"The framed window around the Canvas (including scrollbars, rulers, and the document tab) is called the Document Window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19031","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Document Window","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19031"}}},{"id":"Image_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_61","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"Inside of the Document Window, you will find several parts to help you learn more about your project. Click on the Document Tab to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_21","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30110","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30139","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"The tab at the top of each open file showing the document’s filename is the Document Tab; if you have multiple projects open, click a tab to switch between open images.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19164","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Document Tab","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":738},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19164"}}},{"id":"Image_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_62","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":"Another part that you will see is the Status Bar.  Click on the Status Bar to learn more. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_10","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_23","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30419","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si30448","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_108","title":"This is the horizontal bar at the bottom of the document window that shows key information such as the current zoom percentage, save progress, and other details about your file. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide19367","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Status Bar","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":576},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide19367"}}},{"id":"Image_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_63","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_83","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"Lastly, you will see something floating around while you are working - the Contextual Toolbar!  Click on the Contextual Toolbar to learn more about it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_12","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_24","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si70556","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si70571","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_109","title":"The Contextual Toolbar is a dynamic toolbar that appears when using certain tools or when specific objects are selected, offering one-click access to related commands. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide70587","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace - Contextual Tool Bar","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":669},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide70587"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"Knowledge Check: Label Workspace Components Drag and drop the correct component label to where it belongs. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si28448","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si28477","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Image_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_26","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Home_Button","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_4","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_2","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_5","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_3","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_6","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_4","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_7","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_5","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_8","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_6","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_9","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_7","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_10","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_8","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_11","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_9","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_12","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_10","roles":{}},{"id":"Home_Button_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Home_Button_14","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Line_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Line_12","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"Home Button ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":"Menu Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"Options Bar  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_41","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":"Document Tab  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_42","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"Document Window ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":"Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"Status Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":"Contextual Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"Canvas ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":"Collapsed Panels ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_48","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"Expanded Panels ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_33","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si174356","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si174385","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_8","title":"Not quite!  Take some time to review and try again. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_8","title":"Great Job!Now that you know where the components are, let’s move on.  Click Next to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16044","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16061","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16074","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16209","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16226","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si16239","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide14555","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Workspace Knowledge Check","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":18900},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14555"},"dragDrop":{"sources":[14483,14490,14497,14504,14511,14518,14525,14532,14539,14568,14581],"targets":[15108,15166,15202,15242,15280,15318,15356,15394,15432,15480,15567]}}},{"id":"Image_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_105","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_15","title":"Customizing Your Workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_63","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si279958","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si279973","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide279989","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Customizing Your Workspace","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":255},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide279989"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_160","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_160","title":"You will find all of the workspace options by selecting the Window menu.  Workspace is the second option and will show a submenu when the mouse reaches it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_161","title":"The Essentials (Default) is what we have been looking at so far.  Anytime changes are made, you can always reset your workspace from the same submenu as you see here. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_162","title":"Once you get a better idea of how your workflow will be and what your most used tools and panels are, you can actually move things around. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide233120","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Reset Essentials Workspace","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":891},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide233120"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_163","title":"Once you get a better idea of how your workflow will be and what your most used tools and panels are, you can actually move things around. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide234216","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Moving Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":312},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide234216"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_168","title":"I went ahead and customized the workspace to fit my workflow. Let’s look at how to save it for access anytime! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide234530","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Saving Workspace","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":300},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide234530"}}},{"id":"Image_126","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_126","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_21","title":"Saving A Custom Workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_77","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_77","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si429308","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si429323","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide429339","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Customizing Panel Locations","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":225},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide429339"}}},{"id":"Step_105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_105","title":"Step 1: Click the Window Menu ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide429370","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Saving Step 1","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":292},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide429370"}}},{"id":"Step_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_106","title":"Step 2: Select and Open the Workspace submenu ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide429417","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"saving step 2","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":190},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide429417"}}},{"id":"Step_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_107","title":"Step 3: Click on New Workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide429488","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"saving step 3","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":186},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide429488"}}},{"id":"Step_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_108","title":"Step 4: In the New Workspace dialog box, type in a name, check the boxes of what you want saved for that workspace, then click Save. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide429559","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"saving step 4","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":492},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide429559"}}},{"id":"Step_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_109","title":"Step 5. Go back to the Workspace submenu and check that your new workspace is listed. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_323","title":"Now you try!  In the next section, you will be able to click on the screen to follow the steps that pop up and save a custom workspace.  Click Next to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_78","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_78","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si429833","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si429862","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide429608","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"saving step 5","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":678},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide429608"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_27","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_44","title":"Task 1:  Open the Window Menu ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_17","title":"Where is the Menu Bar located? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_11","title":"You found the Window Menu! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide247914","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":183},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide247914"}}},{"id":"Slide247970","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":15},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide247970"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_28","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_47","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_47","title":"Task 2:  Select New Workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_18","title":"What submenu option  should you click? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_12","title":"You found the New Workspace option! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide247989","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":231},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide247989"}}},{"id":"Slide248045","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":15},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248045"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_5","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":true,"answers":["My New Workspace"]},"constraints":{"length":-1}}}},{"id":"Step_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_49","title":"Task 3:  Name this custom setup My New Workspace (Hint: Make sure you have the capitalization and spaces exactly as it appears above) ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_19","title":"Try Again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_13","title":"Name your custom workspace here ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248064","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":411},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248064"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_29","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_50","title":"Task 4:  Check the box next to Keyboard Shortcuts ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_20","title":"Try Again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_14","title":"Select these options if you have made changes for your workspace to save ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248127","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":159},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248127"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_32","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_51","title":"Task 5:  Save your workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_23","title":"Try Again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_17","title":"Click the Save button ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248295","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248295"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_33","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_52","title":"Task 6:  Check that “My New Workspace” apears in the Workspace submenu ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_24","title":"What Menu should you choose? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_18","title":"You found it! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248351","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248351"}}},{"id":"Step_53","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_53","title":"Task 6:  Check that “My New Workspace” apears in the Workspace submenu ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248407","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":15},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248407"}}},{"id":"Step_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_55","title":"Task 6:  Check that “My New Workspace” apears in the Workspace submenu ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Step_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_54","title":"Is it there? ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_44","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si249268","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si249297","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_45","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_45","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si249400","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si249429","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide248426","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":60},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248426"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_34","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_56","title":"Task 7:  Select the Essentials Workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_25","title":"Select the Essentials (Default) menu item ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_19","title":"You found it! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248445","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248445"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_35","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_57","title":"Task 8:  Change back to My New Workspace to see the changes you just saved! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_26","title":"Try Again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_20","title":"Awesome! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248501","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248501"}}},{"id":"Step_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_58","title":"Task 8:  Change back to My New Workspace to see the changes you just saved! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248557","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":15},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248557"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_36","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Step_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_59","title":"Task 8:  Change back to My New Workspace to see the changes you just saved! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_27","title":"Try Again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_21","title":"Select My New Workspace ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide248576","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248576"}}},{"id":"Step_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_60","title":"Task 8:  Change back to My New Workspace to see the changes you just saved! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Step_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Step_61","title":"Awesome job!  Now let’s learn how to open, move, and close panels so you can customize your own workspace in the future. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_46","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_46","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si249977","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si250006","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide248632","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":432},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide248632"}}},{"id":"Image_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_106","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_16","title":"Customizing Panel Locations ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_64","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si280093","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si280108","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide280124","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Customizing Panel Locations","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":270},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide280124"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_181","title":"To move panels around the workspace, simply click and drag the title tab of a panel to where you want it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_182","title":"When moving a panel around, watch for the blue highlights that wil appear. The highlights show you where the panel will go if inside the Panel Dock. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide250177","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Moving Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":807},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide250177"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_187","title":"To open or close a Collapsed Panel, click on the panel’s icon that you need. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_188","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_188","title":"By moving your mouse to the bottom of or between panels, you can resize them to see all they have to offer. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_189","title":"All panels have this symbol of stacked lines in their top right corner. I refer to this as the Pancake menu. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_190","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_190","title":"To close a panel or group, click on the Pancake Menu and select Close or Close Tab Group at the bottom. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_191","title":"Now, let’s look at how to open panels as we need them in the workspace. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_65","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_66","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_67","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide250738","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":2259},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide250738"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_192","title":"Now, let’s look at how to open panels as we need them in the workspace. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_150","title":"The panels are located under the same menu that we found the workspaces!  Go ahead and open the Window menu. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_19","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_3","title":"Click the Window menu at the top of your screen to see a list of all Panels available in Photoshop. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide222606","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Opening Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":264},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide222606"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_147","title":"Below Workspace in the Window menu, all panels available are shown in alphabetical order. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_62","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_62","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_151","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_151","title":"If a panel has a checkmark next to it’s name, then it is open inside your workspace already.  If not, you can click on a panel to open it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_63","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_63","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_152","title":"As you can see, none are open yet! Let’s start by opening the most used Panel in Photoshop: the Layers panel.  Click Layers in the Window menu to open it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_64","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Click_Box_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_20","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_4","title":"Let’s open the most used Panel in Photoshop: the Layers Panel. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide222662","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Opening Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":699},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide222662"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_148","title":"Awesome work!  Our Layers Panel automatically opened on the right side of our screen! Some panels will open with others, as this one did, because it is part of a group of associated panels that are typically used together. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_193","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_193","title":"Let’s go ahead and open another panel so you can get a little more practice.  Click Next to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_37","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si232454","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si232483","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide222718","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Opening Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":471},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide222718"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_23","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_149","title":"Open the Properties Panel using the steps you just learned. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_7","title":"Step 1: The Window menu is where you find the list of Panels. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide231873","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Opening Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":471},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide231873"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_153","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_153","title":"Open the Properties Panel using the steps you just learned. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide231929","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Opening Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":30},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide231929"}}},{"id":"Click_Box_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Click_Box_24","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_154","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_154","title":"Open the Properties Panel using the steps you just learned. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_8","title":"Step 2: The Properties Panel is the second most used panel in Photoshop. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide231948","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Opening Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":471},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide231948"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_155","title":"Great work!  As you can see, the Properties Panel opens in a tab group like the Layers Panel. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_156","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_156","title":"Now you know how to open a Panel to use in your workspace.  Click Next to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_38","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si232913","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si232942","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide232004","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Opening Panels","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":498},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide232004"}}},{"id":"Image_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_120","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_18","title":"Key Takeaways & Additional Resources ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_67","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si417862","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si417877","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide417893","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"The Essentials Workspace","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":216},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide417893"}}},{"id":"Image_124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_124","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_20","title":"By now, you should be able to: ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_318","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_318","title":"Identify and label the main workspace components inside of Adobe Photoshop  Navigate the Essentials default workspace  Reset, customize and save a workspace ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_320","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_320","title":"Looking for more information? Check out these helpful articles below! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_71","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_71","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418374","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418395","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_73","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418524","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418545","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_72","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_72","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418449","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418470","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Button_75","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_75","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418723","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si418752","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide418111","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Course Objectives","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":630},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide418111"}}},{"id":"Image_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_107","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Title_AutoShape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_17","title":"IT’S QUIZ TIME!  There are 15 questions total. You must score 80% or higher to complete this course. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_65","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si280228","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si280243","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide280259","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"QUIZ - 15 questions","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":420},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide280259"}}},{"id":"Slide271624","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271624"}}},{"id":"Slide273107","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":268298,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide273107"}}},{"id":"Slide271649","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271649"}}},{"id":"Slide271674","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271674"}}},{"id":"Slide273132","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":268298,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide273132"}}},{"id":"Slide271699","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271699"}}},{"id":"Slide271724","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271724"}}},{"id":"Slide273157","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":268298,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide273157"}}},{"id":"Slide271749","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271749"}}},{"id":"Slide271774","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271774"}}},{"id":"Slide273182","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":268298,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide273182"}}},{"id":"Slide271799","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271799"}}},{"id":"Slide271824","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271824"}}},{"id":"Slide273207","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":268298,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide273207"}}},{"id":"Slide271849","class":"Random Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","pool":423,"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":0},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271849"}}},{"id":"Image_108","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_108","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":379,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_309","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_309","title":"QUIZ RESULTS ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_97","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_97","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22970","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si22978","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si22986","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si273261","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Retake Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"retake","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Retake Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"retake","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273291","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Retake Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"retake","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22998","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si22966","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22974","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"out of ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Score: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23002","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Get Certificate ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23019","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Get Certificate ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23032","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Get Certificate ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22929","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22929"}}},{"id":"Image_73","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_73","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"question":{"quizId":-1,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_68","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_121","title":"$$Captivate_LearnerName$$ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_132","title":"Learner Contact Email:  $$Captivate_LearnerEmail$$ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_136","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_136","title":"Introduction to the Adobe Photoshop Workspace ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_137","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_137","title":"$$cpInfoCurrentDateString$$ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_195","title":"(c) 2025    MADE IN ADOBE CAPTIVATE CLASSIC         Author: Rachel N. Lagrange, Certified Adobe Educator (Lvl 2) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_196","title":"COURSE LENGTH: 45 minutes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_89","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_99","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_99","title":"Quiz Score:  $$cpInfoPercentage$$% ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide203685","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"Certificate of Completion","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":300},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide203685"}}},{"id":"Image_101","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_101","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270049q"},"question":{"interactionId":"269881","quizId":379,"text":"Image ","type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269925","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_203","roles":{}},{"id":"si269902","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":"Select the Contextual Toolbar from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269919hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_43","roles":{}},{"id":"si269919","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269955","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_35","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270049q","for":"Slide270049q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269967","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270049q","for":"Slide270049q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270049q","for":"Slide270049q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269993hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_44","roles":{}},{"id":"si269993","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270007hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_45","roles":{}},{"id":"si270007","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270021hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_46","roles":{}},{"id":"si270021","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270035hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_47","roles":{}},{"id":"si270035","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348537","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Be sure to select an answer to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270049q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348556","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270049q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348575","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270049q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide270049","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide270049"},"question":{"interactionId":"269874","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Contextual Toolbar from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_109","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268297q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_114","roles":{}},{"id":"si268150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"Select the Canvas from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268167hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_28","roles":{}},{"id":"si268167","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268297q","for":"Slide268297q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268215","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268297q","for":"Slide268297q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268227","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268297q","for":"Slide268297q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268241hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_29","roles":{}},{"id":"si268241","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268255hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_30","roles":{}},{"id":"si268255","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268269hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_31","roles":{}},{"id":"si268269","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268283hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_32","roles":{}},{"id":"si268283","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268297q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348626","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268297q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348639","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268297q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide268297","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide268297"},"question":{"interactionId":"268122","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Canvas from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_110","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268110q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267986","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_112","roles":{}},{"id":"si267963","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"Select the Document Tab from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267980hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_23","roles":{}},{"id":"si267980","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_10","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268110q","for":"Slide268110q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268028","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268110q","for":"Slide268110q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268110q","for":"Slide268110q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268054hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_24","roles":{}},{"id":"si268054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268068hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_25","roles":{}},{"id":"si268068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268082hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_26","roles":{}},{"id":"si268082","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268096hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_27","roles":{}},{"id":"si268096","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348652","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268110q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348665","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268110q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348678","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268110q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide268110","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide268110"},"question":{"interactionId":"267935","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Document Tab from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_111","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_111","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270236q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_204","roles":{}},{"id":"si270089","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Select the Status Bar from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270106hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_48","roles":{}},{"id":"si270106","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_36","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270236q","for":"Slide270236q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270154","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270236q","for":"Slide270236q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270166","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270236q","for":"Slide270236q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270180hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_49","roles":{}},{"id":"si270180","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270194hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_50","roles":{}},{"id":"si270194","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270208hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_51","roles":{}},{"id":"si270208","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270222hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_52","roles":{}},{"id":"si270222","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348691","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270236q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348704","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270236q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348717","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270236q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide270236","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide270236"},"question":{"interactionId":"270061","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Status Bar from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_112","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_112","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269862q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_202","roles":{}},{"id":"si269715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Select the Document Window from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269732hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_38","roles":{}},{"id":"si269732","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269768","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_31","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269862q","for":"Slide269862q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269780","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269862q","for":"Slide269862q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269792","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269862q","for":"Slide269862q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269806hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_39","roles":{}},{"id":"si269806","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269820hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_40","roles":{}},{"id":"si269820","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269834hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_41","roles":{}},{"id":"si269834","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269848hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_42","roles":{}},{"id":"si269848","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269862q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348743","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269862q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269862q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide269862","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide269862"},"question":{"interactionId":"269687","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Document Window from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_113","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269675q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269551","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_201","roles":{}},{"id":"si269528","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":"Select the Expanded Panels from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269545hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_33","roles":{}},{"id":"si269545","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269581","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_30","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269675q","for":"Slide269675q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269675q","for":"Slide269675q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269605","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269675q","for":"Slide269675q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269619hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_34","roles":{}},{"id":"si269619","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269633hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_35","roles":{}},{"id":"si269633","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269647hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_36","roles":{}},{"id":"si269647","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si269661hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_37","roles":{}},{"id":"si269661","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348769","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269675q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348782","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269675q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348795","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269675q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide269675","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide269675"},"question":{"interactionId":"269500","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Expanded Panels from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["4"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_114","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_114","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267736q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267612","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_99","roles":{}},{"id":"si267589","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"Select the Collapsed Panels from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267606hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_13","roles":{}},{"id":"si267606","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267736q","for":"Slide267736q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267654","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267736q","for":"Slide267736q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267666","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267736q","for":"Slide267736q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267680hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_14","roles":{}},{"id":"si267680","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267694hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_15","roles":{}},{"id":"si267694","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267708hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_16","roles":{}},{"id":"si267708","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267722hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_17","roles":{}},{"id":"si267722","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267736q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348821","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267736q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267736q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide267736","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide267736"},"question":{"interactionId":"267561","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Collapsed Panels from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["4"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_115","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_115","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267549q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267425","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_98","roles":{}},{"id":"si267402","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_18","title":"Select the Toolbar from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267419hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_8","roles":{}},{"id":"si267419","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267549q","for":"Slide267549q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267467","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267549q","for":"Slide267549q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267479","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267549q","for":"Slide267549q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267493hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_9","roles":{}},{"id":"si267493","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267507hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_10","roles":{}},{"id":"si267507","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267521hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_11","roles":{}},{"id":"si267521","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267535hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_12","roles":{}},{"id":"si267535","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348847","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267549q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267549q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348873","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267549q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide267549","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide267549"},"question":{"interactionId":"267374","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Toolbar from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_116","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266946q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267036","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si266976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Select the Options Bar from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266983hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_3","roles":{}},{"id":"si266983","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266946q","for":"Slide266946q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267057","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266946q","for":"Slide266946q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266946q","for":"Slide266946q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267288hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_4","roles":{}},{"id":"si267288","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267303hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_5","roles":{}},{"id":"si267303","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267318hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_6","roles":{}},{"id":"si267318","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267333hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_7","roles":{}},{"id":"si267333","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266946q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348899","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266946q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266946q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide266946","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide266946"},"question":{"interactionId":"266963","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Options Bar from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["0"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_117","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267923q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267799","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_104","roles":{}},{"id":"si267776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"Select the Menu Bar from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267793hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_18","roles":{}},{"id":"si267793","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267829","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267923q","for":"Slide267923q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267841","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267923q","for":"Slide267923q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide267923q","for":"Slide267923q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si267867hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_19","roles":{}},{"id":"si267867","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267881hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_20","roles":{}},{"id":"si267881","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267895hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_21","roles":{}},{"id":"si267895","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si267909hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_22","roles":{}},{"id":"si267909","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348925","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267923q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348938","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267923q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348951","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide267923q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide267923","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide267923"},"question":{"interactionId":"267748","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Menu Bar from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["0"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_118","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_118","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270423q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270299","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_205","roles":{}},{"id":"si270276","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"Select the Home Button from the highlighted areas below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270293hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_53","roles":{}},{"id":"si270293","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_39","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270423q","for":"Slide270423q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270341","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270423q","for":"Slide270423q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270423q","for":"Slide270423q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270367hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_54","roles":{}},{"id":"si270367","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270381hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_55","roles":{}},{"id":"si270381","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270395hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_56","roles":{}},{"id":"si270395","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si270409hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_57","roles":{}},{"id":"si270409","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si348964","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270423q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348977","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270423q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si348990","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270423q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide270423","class":"Question Slide","instance":"Quiz","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide270423"},"question":{"interactionId":"270248","quizId":-1,"title":"Hot Spot","text":"Select the Home Button from the highlighted areas below.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":423,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["4"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_90","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_90","title":"The icon (usually top-left) that takes you back to Photoshop’s Home screen, where you can open recent files, browse presets, and access Learn tutorials. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269488q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269420","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_200","roles":{}},{"id":"si269358","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_26","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_170","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269373","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_171","title":"Document Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269369_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si269380","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_172","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269384","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_174","title":"Canvas ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269380_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_18","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canvas\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si269391","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_183","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269395","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_197","title":"Home Button ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269391_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_19","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Home Button\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si269402","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_198","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269406","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_199","title":"Status Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269402_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Status Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si269450","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_26","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269488q","for":"Slide269488q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269462","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269488q","for":"Slide269488q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269488q","for":"Slide269488q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349045","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269488q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349071","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect- It is the Home Button.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269488q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide269488","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide269488"},"question":{"interactionId":"269312","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_89","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_89","title":"The central area where your image’s pixels actually live—this is where you paint, edit, and compose. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269289q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_169","roles":{}},{"id":"si269159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269170","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_143","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_144","title":"Document Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269170_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si269181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_145","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_146","title":"Canvas ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269181_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_14","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canvas\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si269192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_157","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269196","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_158","title":"Document Window ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269192_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Window\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si269203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_159","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269207","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_164","title":"Status Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269203_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_16","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Status Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si269251","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_25","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269289q","for":"Slide269289q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269263","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269289q","for":"Slide269289q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269275","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269289q","for":"Slide269289q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269289q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect -  It is the Canvas. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269289q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide269289","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide269289"},"question":{"interactionId":"269113","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_88","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_88","title":"A dynamic toolbar that appears when using certain tools (like Type or Crop) or when specific objects are selected, offering one-click access to related commands (for example, alignment options or text formatting). ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269084q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269016","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_142","roles":{}},{"id":"si268954","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268965","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_127","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268969","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_128","title":"Document Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268965_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_9","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268976","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_130","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268980","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_131","title":"Contextual Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268976_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_10","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contextual Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si268987","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_138","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268991","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_139","title":"Document Window ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268987_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_11","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Window\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268998","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_140","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269002","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_141","title":"Status Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268998_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_12","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Status Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si269046","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269084q","for":"Slide269084q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269058","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269084q","for":"Slide269084q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si269070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide269084q","for":"Slide269084q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269084q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349123","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is the Contextual Toolbar. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide269084q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide269084","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide269084"},"question":{"interactionId":"268908","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_87","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_87","title":"The horizontal bar beneath the Menu Bar that displays settings specific to whichever tool is active (for example, brush size and hardness when the Brush tool is selected). ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268879q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268811","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_126","roles":{}},{"id":"si268749","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268760","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_116","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268764","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_117","title":"Status Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268760_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Status Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268771","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_118","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268775","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_119","title":"Options Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268771_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Options Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si268782","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_120","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268786","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_122","title":"Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268782_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268793","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_123","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268797","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_125","title":"Canvas ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268793_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canvas\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268841","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268879q","for":"Slide268879q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268879q","for":"Slide268879q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268865","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268879q","for":"Slide268879q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349136","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268879q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349149","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is the Options Bar. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268879q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide268879","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide268879"},"question":{"interactionId":"268703","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_86","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_86","title":"The horizontal bar at the bottom of the document window that shows key information such as the current zoom percentage, document dimensions and profile, save or rendering progress, and other contextual details about your file. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268446q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268556","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si268483","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268498","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Status Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268498_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Status Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si268509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268513","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Home Button ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268509_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Home Button\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268625","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268629","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268625_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268640","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268644","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Canvas ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268640_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canvas\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si268560","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268446q","for":"Slide268446q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268577","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268446q","for":"Slide268446q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268590","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide268446q","for":"Slide268446q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349162","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268446q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349175","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is the Status Bar. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide268446q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide268446","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide268446"},"question":{"interactionId":"268463","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_96","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_96","title":"The top-most horizontal bar containing drop-down menus (“File,” “Edit,” “Image,” “Layer,” etc.) that give access to every command and feature in Photoshop. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271623q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271555","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_259","roles":{}},{"id":"si271493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_251","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271508","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_252","title":"Contextual Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271504_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contextual Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_253","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271519","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_254","title":"Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271515_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_42","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271526","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_255","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271530","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_256","title":"Menu Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271526_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_43","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Menu Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si271537","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_257","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271541","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_258","title":"Options Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271537_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_44","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Options Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271585","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_51","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271623q","for":"Slide271623q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271597","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271623q","for":"Slide271623q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271623q","for":"Slide271623q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271623q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349201","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is the Menu Bar. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271623q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide271623","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271623"},"question":{"interactionId":"271447","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_95","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_95","title":"The vertical strip of tool icons (on the left by default) for all your drawing, selection, and editing tools—Move, Marquee, Brush, Clone Stamp, etc. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271424q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271356","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_250","roles":{}},{"id":"si271294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271305","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_242","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271309","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_243","title":"Contextual Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271305_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_37","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contextual Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_244","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271320","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_245","title":"Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271316_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_38","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si271327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_246","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_247","title":"Menu Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271327_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_39","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Menu Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271338","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_248","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271342","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_249","title":"Options Bar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271338_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Options Bar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_50","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271424q","for":"Slide271424q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271398","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271424q","for":"Slide271424q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271410","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271424q","for":"Slide271424q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349214","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271424q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349227","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is the Toolbar. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271424q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide271424","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271424"},"question":{"interactionId":"271248","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_94","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_94","title":"The framed window around the canvas (including scrollbars, rulers, and the document tab) that contains all the visual workspace for that particular file. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271225q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_241","roles":{}},{"id":"si271095","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_233","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_234","title":"Contextual Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271106_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_33","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contextual Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_235","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_236","title":"Canvas ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271117_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_34","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canvas\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_237","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_238","title":"Document Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271128_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_35","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_239","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271143","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_240","title":"Document Window ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271139_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_36","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Window\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si271187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_49","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271225q","for":"Slide271225q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271199","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271225q","for":"Slide271225q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271211","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271225q","for":"Slide271225q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349282","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271225q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349295","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is the Document Window. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271225q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide271225","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271225"},"question":{"interactionId":"271049","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_93","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_93","title":"The tab at the top of each open file window showing the document’s filename; click a tab to switch between open images. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271026q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270958","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_232","roles":{}},{"id":"si270896","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270907","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_224","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270911","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_225","title":"Contextual Toolbar ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270907_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_29","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Contextual Toolbar\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270918","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_226","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270922","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_227","title":"Canvas ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270918_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_30","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Canvas\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270929","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_228","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270933","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_229","title":"Document Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270929_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_31","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si270940","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_230","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270944","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_231","title":"Document Window ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270940_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_32","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Window\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270988","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_48","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271026q","for":"Slide271026q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271000","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271026q","for":"Slide271026q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide271026q","for":"Slide271026q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271026q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349321","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is the Document Tab. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide271026q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide271026","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide271026"},"question":{"interactionId":"270850","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_92","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_92","title":"Fully open panel groups (usually along the right side) showing all their controls—like Layers, Properties, and Adjustments—so you can access detailed settings at a glance. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270821q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270753","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_223","roles":{}},{"id":"si270691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270702","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_215","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270706","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_216","title":"Collapsed Panels ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270702_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_25","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Collapsed Panels\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270713","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_217","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_218","title":"Expanded Panels ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270713_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_26","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Expanded Panels\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si270724","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_219","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_220","title":"Document Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270724_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_27","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270735","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_221","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_222","title":"Document Window ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270735_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Window\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270783","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_47","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270821q","for":"Slide270821q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270795","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270821q","for":"Slide270821q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270807","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270821q","for":"Slide270821q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270821q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - It is Expanded Panels. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270821q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide270821","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide270821"},"question":{"interactionId":"270645","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_91","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_91","title":"Minimized panel icons that hide their contents until you hover or click, helping keep your workspace uncluttered while still giving quick access when needed. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270622q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270554","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_214","roles":{}},{"id":"si270492","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"Choose the correct term for the definition below. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270503","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_206","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_207","title":"Collapsed Panels ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270503_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"2_21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Collapsed Panels\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si270514","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_208","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270518","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_209","title":"Expanded Panels ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270514_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"4_22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Expanded Panels\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270525","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_210","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270529","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_211","title":"Document Tab ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270525_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"6_23","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Tab\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_212","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270540","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_213","title":"Document Window ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270536_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"8_24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Document Window\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si270584","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_41","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270622q","for":"Slide270622q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270596","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270622q","for":"Slide270622q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si270608","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide270622q","for":"Slide270622q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349360","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270622q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349373","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide270622q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide270622","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide270622"},"question":{"interactionId":"270446","quizId":-1,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Choose the correct term for the definition below.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":423,"interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_85","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_85","title":"SAVING A CUSTOM WORKSPACE ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266809q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266900","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si266840","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Drag and drop the steps into the correct order. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266847","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si266856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"1. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266860","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si266860c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Open the Window menu ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si266866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"2. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266870","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si266870c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Select New Workspace from the Workspace submenu ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"3. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268381","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si268381c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Name the workspace Caroline’s Setup ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268388","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"4. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268392","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si268392c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Check the Keyboard Shortcuts box ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268399","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"5. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268403","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si268403c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Press the Save button ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si268427","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"6. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si268431","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si268431c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Check that Caroline’s Setup is in the Workspace submenu ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si266904","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266809q","for":"Slide266809q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266921","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266809q","for":"Slide266809q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266934","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266809q","for":"Slide266809q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266809q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349402","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266809q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide266809","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide266809"},"question":{"interactionId":"266826","quizId":-1,"title":"Sequence","text":"Drag and drop the steps into the correct order.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"pool":268298,"interactionType":"sequencing","ramdomized":true,"correctAnswers":["si266860c","si266870c","si268381c","si268392c","si268403c","si268431c"],"score":{"weight":5,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si266624","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si266551","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You can save a custom workspace setup by going to File > Workspace > New Workspace ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266566","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266570","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266566_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si266577","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266581","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266577_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si266628","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266514q","for":"Slide266514q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266645","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266514q","for":"Slide266514q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si266658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide266514q","for":"Slide266514q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349418","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266514q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349431","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is False. You can save a custom workspace setup by going to  Window > Workspace > New Workspace  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide266514q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide266514","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide266514"},"question":{"interactionId":"266531","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"You can save a custom workspace setup by going to\rFile > Workspace > New Workspace\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si272627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_289","roles":{}},{"id":"si272588","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"You can save a custom workspace setup by going to Window > Workspace > New Workspace ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272599","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_285","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272603","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_286","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272599_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"56","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272610","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_287","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272614","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_288","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272610_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"58","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272657","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_57","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272695q","for":"Slide272695q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272669","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272695q","for":"Slide272695q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272681","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272695q","for":"Slide272695q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349444","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272695q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349457","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is True. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272695q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272695","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272695"},"question":{"interactionId":"272573","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"You can save a custom workspace setup by going to\rWindow > Workspace > New Workspace\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si271942","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_264","roles":{}},{"id":"si271903","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":"You can switch to the Essentials Workspace by going to Window > Workspace > Essentials (Default) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271914","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_260","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271918","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_261","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271914_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271925","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_262","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271929","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_263","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271925_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si271972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_52","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272010q","for":"Slide272010q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272010q","for":"Slide272010q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si271996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272010q","for":"Slide272010q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349470","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272010q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349483","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is True. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272010q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272010","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272010"},"question":{"interactionId":"271888","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"You can switch to the Essentials Workspace by going to\rWindow > Workspace > Essentials (Default)\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si272079","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_269","roles":{}},{"id":"si272040","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"You can click the Pancake menu in any panel to close it. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272051","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_265","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272055","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_266","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272051_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45_48","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272062","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_267","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272066","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_268","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272062_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47_49","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_53","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272147q","for":"Slide272147q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272147q","for":"Slide272147q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272133","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272147q","for":"Slide272147q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349496","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272147q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is True. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272147q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272147","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272147"},"question":{"interactionId":"272025","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"You can click the Pancake menu in any panel to close it.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si272216","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_274","roles":{}},{"id":"si272177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":"You can click the Pancake menu to open a panel. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272188","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_270","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_271","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272188_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45_50","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272199","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_272","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_273","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272199_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47_51","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272246","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_54","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272284q","for":"Slide272284q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272284q","for":"Slide272284q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272284q","for":"Slide272284q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349522","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272284q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349535","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is False. You can click the Pancake menu to close a panel, not open it. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272284q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272284","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272284"},"question":{"interactionId":"272162","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"You can click the Pancake menu to open a panel.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si272353","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_279","roles":{}},{"id":"si272314","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"You can find all available panels under the Window menu. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272325","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_275","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272329","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_276","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272325_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45_52","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272336","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_277","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272340","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_278","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272336_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47_53","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272383","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_55","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272421q","for":"Slide272421q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272395","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272421q","for":"Slide272421q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272407","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272421q","for":"Slide272421q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349548","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272421q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349561","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is True. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272421q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272421","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272421"},"question":{"interactionId":"272299","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"You can find all available panels under the Window menu.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si272490","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_284","roles":{}},{"id":"si272451","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":"You cannot find all available panels under the View menu. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_280","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_281","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272462_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45_54","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_282","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_283","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272473_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47_55","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272520","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_56","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272558q","for":"Slide272558q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272532","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272558q","for":"Slide272558q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272544","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272558q","for":"Slide272558q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272558q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349587","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is True. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272558q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272558","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272558"},"question":{"interactionId":"272436","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"You cannot find all available panels under the View menu.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si272764","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_294","roles":{}},{"id":"si272725","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":"Collapsed and Expanded Panels can both be found in the Panel Dock on the right side of the workspace. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272736","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_290","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272740","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_291","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272736_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45_59","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272747","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_292","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272751","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_293","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272747_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47_60","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_58","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272832q","for":"Slide272832q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272806","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272832q","for":"Slide272832q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272818","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272832q","for":"Slide272832q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349600","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272832q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is True. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272832q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272832","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272832"},"question":{"interactionId":"272710","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"Collapsed and Expanded Panels can both be found in the Panel Dock on the right side of the workspace.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si272901","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_299","roles":{}},{"id":"si272862","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_57","title":"Clicking the Home Button while in the workspace takes you to the Home Screen of Photoshop. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272873","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_295","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_296","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272873_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45_61","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272884","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_297","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272888","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272884_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47_62","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si272931","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_59","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272969q","for":"Slide272969q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272943","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272969q","for":"Slide272969q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si272955","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide272969q","for":"Slide272969q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349626","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272969q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349639","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is True. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide272969q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide272969","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide272969"},"question":{"interactionId":"272847","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"Clicking the Home Button while in the workspace takes you to the Home Screen of Photoshop.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si273038","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_304","roles":{}},{"id":"si272999","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_58","title":"Panels cannot be moved around the workspace as they are stuck to the Panel Dock. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273010","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_300","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273014","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_301","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273010_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"45_63","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si273021","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_302","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_303","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273021_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"47_64","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si273068","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_60","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide273106q","for":"Slide273106q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide273106q","for":"Slide273106q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si273092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide273106q","for":"Slide273106q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349652","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide273106q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si349665","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - This statement is False. Panels can be moved around the Workspace. They are not stuck only to the Panel Dock. Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide273106q"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide273106","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide273106"},"question":{"interactionId":"272984","quizId":-1,"title":"True/False","text":"Panels cannot be moved around the workspace as they are stuck to the Panel Dock.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","pool":268298,"interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"WorkspaceElements","questions":["269874","268122","267935","270061","269687","269500","267561","267374","266963","267748","270248","269312","269113","268908","268703","268463","271447","271248","271049","270850","270645","270446"]}}},{"id":"Pool268298","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":268298,"name":"WorkspaceQuestions","questions":["266826","266531","271888","272025","272162","272299","272436","272573","272710","272847","272984"]}}},{"id":"D2991_Task 1_ROUGH_FINAL","class":"project","title":"D2991_Task 1_ROUGH_FINAL","children":["Slide7703","Slide203976","Slide7757","Slide7932","Slide8494","Slide233903","Slide246390","Slide17712","Slide18364","Slide18481","Slide18590","Slide18709","Slide195340","Slide18836","Slide19031","Slide19164","Slide19367","Slide70587","Slide14555","Slide279989","Slide233120","Slide234216","Slide234530","Slide429339","Slide429370","Slide429417","Slide429488","Slide429559","Slide429608","Slide247914","Slide247970","Slide247989","Slide248045","Slide248064","Slide248127","Slide248295","Slide248351","Slide248407","Slide248426","Slide248445","Slide248501","Slide248557","Slide248576","Slide248632","Slide280124","Slide250177","Slide250738","Slide222606","Slide222662","Slide222718","Slide231873","Slide231929","Slide231948","Slide232004","Slide417893","Slide418111","Slide280259","Slide271624","Slide273107","Slide271649","Slide271674","Slide273132","Slide271699","Slide271724","Slide273157","Slide271749","Slide271774","Slide273182","Slide271799","Slide271824","Slide273207","Slide271849","Slide22929","Slide203685"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":false,"questions":["rqSlide271624","rqSlide273107","rqSlide271649","rqSlide271674","rqSlide273132","rqSlide271699","rqSlide271724","rqSlide273157","rqSlide271749","rqSlide271774","rqSlide273182","rqSlide271799","rqSlide271824","rqSlide273207","rqSlide271849"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":150,"passScore":120}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"navigationEnabled":true,"navigateVisitedSlides":false,"collapseAll":false,"showTopicDuration":false,"statusFlag":true,"selfPaced":true,"showSearch":false,"enabled":true},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":false,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":false}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide7703","title":"Title","visible":true},{"id":"Slide203976","title":"Student Information","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7757","title":"Course Objectives","visible":true},{"id":"Slide7932","title":"Photoshop Home Screen","visible":true},{"id":"Slide8494","title":"Photoshop Workspace","visible":true},{"id":"Slide233903","title":"The Essentials Workspace","visible":true},{"id":"Slide246390","title":"Workspace with no project","visible":false},{"id":"Slide17712","title":"Workspace - Home Button","visible":false},{"id":"Slide18364","title":"Workspace - Menu Bar","visible":false},{"id":"Slide18481","title":"Workspace - Toolbar","visible":false},{"id":"Slide18590","title":"Workspace - Options Bar","visible":false},{"id":"Slide18709","title":"Workspace - Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide195340","title":"Workspace - Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide18836","title":"Workspace - Canvas","visible":false},{"id":"Slide19031","title":"Workspace - Document Window","visible":false},{"id":"Slide19164","title":"Workspace - Document Tab","visible":false},{"id":"Slide19367","title":"Workspace - Status Bar","visible":false},{"id":"Slide70587","title":"Workspace - Contextual Tool Bar","visible":false},{"id":"Slide14555","title":"Workspace Knowledge Check","visible":true},{"id":"Slide279989","title":"Customizing Your Workspace","visible":true},{"id":"Slide233120","title":"Reset Essentials Workspace","visible":false},{"id":"Slide234216","title":"Moving Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide429339","title":"Customizing Panel Locations","visible":false},{"id":"Slide234530","title":"Saving Workspace","visible":false},{"id":"Slide429370","title":"Slide 25","visible":false},{"id":"Slide429417","title":"Slide 26","visible":false},{"id":"Slide429488","title":"Slide 27","visible":false},{"id":"Slide429559","title":"Slide 28","visible":false},{"id":"Slide429608","title":"Slide 29","visible":false},{"id":"Slide247914","title":"Slide 24","visible":false},{"id":"Slide247970","title":"Slide 25","visible":false},{"id":"Slide247989","title":"Slide 26","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248045","title":"Slide 27","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248064","title":"Slide 28","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248127","title":"Slide 29","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248295","title":"Slide 30","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248351","title":"Slide 31","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248407","title":"Slide 32","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248426","title":"Slide 33","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248445","title":"Slide 34","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248501","title":"Slide 35","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248557","title":"Slide 36","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248576","title":"Slide 37","visible":false},{"id":"Slide248632","title":"Slide 38","visible":false},{"id":"Slide280124","title":"Customizing Panel Locations","visible":true},{"id":"Slide250177","title":"Moving Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide250738","title":"Slide 41","visible":false},{"id":"Slide222606","title":"Opening Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide222662","title":"Opening Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide222718","title":"Opening Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide231873","title":"Opening Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide231929","title":"Opening Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide231948","title":"Opening Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide232004","title":"Opening Panels","visible":false},{"id":"Slide417893","title":"The Essentials Workspace","visible":false},{"id":"Slide418111","title":"Course Objectives","visible":false},{"id":"Slide280259","title":"QUIZ - 15 questions","visible":true},{"id":"Slide271624","title":"Slide 50","visible":false},{"id":"Slide273107","title":"Slide 51","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271649","title":"Slide 52","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271674","title":"Slide 53","visible":false},{"id":"Slide273132","title":"Slide 54","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271699","title":"Slide 55","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271724","title":"Slide 56","visible":false},{"id":"Slide273157","title":"Slide 57","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271749","title":"Slide 58","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271774","title":"Slide 59","visible":false},{"id":"Slide273182","title":"Slide 60","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271799","title":"Slide 61","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271824","title":"Slide 62","visible":false},{"id":"Slide273207","title":"Slide 63","visible":false},{"id":"Slide271849","title":"Slide 64","visible":false},{"id":"Slide203685","title":"Certificate","visible":false}]}